https://orcawhalewatch.com/privacy/

We use cookies and other technologies to understand how you and other visitors use our site, and improve your browsing experience. Learn More ×
HomeGift CardsToursThe Western Explorer IIThe Western Prince IIWhale Watch Flight PackageOur TeamFAQsGetting HereBlogSitemap
Western Prince Whale Watching
TripAdvisor Yelp Facebook Instagram YouTube
Privacy and Cookie PolicyLog DataLike many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.Google AnalyticsWhen someone visits this website, we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone.To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit Google Tools.Use of CookiesCookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.When you visit this website for the first time, a banner informs you of the use of cookies and provides a direct link to this information page. If you confirm your acceptance of cookies by closing the banner, or if you continue to browse the site, you are confirming your consent.Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and remove them, visit About Cookies.org or All About Cookies.org.Google RetargetingWe use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise our services across the Internet. AdWords remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of this website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your computer. Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.Facebook PixelWe use technology called a Facebook Pixel, which is a tiny snippet of JavaScript code that we’ve placed on each of our web pages. We use the Pixel to measure the return on investment of Facebook Ads by reporting on the actions people take after viewing those ads. We also use it to show you more relevant advertisements on Facebook based on your traffic on our Site. Facebook may use cookies, beacons, and similar technology as part of this process.You may opt out of Facebook’s Custom Audience ads by visiting WebChoices: Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer Choice Tool for Web.Web FormsWe collect personally identifiable information through forms on our website, but only if you choose to fill in your information and submit it to us. Common uses of this information include: to allow our staff to contact you to respond to your questions, to allow you to subscribe to an email newsletter, or to allow you to complete an order. The intent of each web form will be clearly labelled.The data submitted through these web forms is stored on our web server for up to 30 days. It is also sent to our corporate email address where it may be stored indefinitely.Booking ServicesWe use a service called Rezdy to process orders for our services. For more information, see the Rezdy privacy policy: https://www.rezdy.com/privacy-policy/Links to External WebsitesThis privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.Embedded Content from other WebsitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.Contact UsFor questions about this privacy policy, contact us at inquire@orcawhalewatch.com Phone Directions Book Tour
